hrboss.com 2014-10-18

# Privacy Policy | HRBoss

This notice sets forth our Privacy Policy. By agreeing to the Terms of Service required to use HRBoss Sites and Software Services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”). Capitalized terms used but not defined in the Privacy Policy have the meanings ascribed to them in the Terms of Service.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
When you or a candidate visit our Careers Sites or use our Service, you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you actively choose to disclose (“Active Information”) and non-personally identifiable information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an aggregate basis as you and others use our Site (“Passive Information”). These two types of information are referred to collectively as “Subscriber Information.”

**Active Information You or Candidate Provide**  
In order to use the Service, we require you and candidates to disclose the following information: full legal name, full company name and a valid e-mail address. Additionally, if you or candidates choose to post information through our Service or engage in email, regular mail, telephone or other contact with us, we may retain information disclosed thereby as well.

**Passive Information Collected**  
Our Site and the Service utilize a standard technology called “cookies” to collect information about how our Site and Service is used. Passive Information gathered may include but is not limited to the date and time of visits, the Site pages viewed, time spent at our Site, a logging of activities, and the sites visited just before and just after our Site.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allow web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Site. They are small pieces of data that we transfer to your computer's hard drive to enable our systems to recognize your browser, simplify subsequent interactions with our Site and streamline your use of the Site.

**System Log**  
When you use our Services, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

  * Details of how user interact with the functionality of the system for troubleshooting purposes when error is detected.
  * Origin of the Internet protocol address.
  * Application event information such as system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of user’s request and referral URL.

**Use of Information Collected**  
We use the information we collect from all of our Services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect HRBoss, our Clients and our Users. Individuals we employ directly, or as Contractors or Agents at our direction, use Active Information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing Subscriber and Candidates Services such as support, and making available other products or services we think may be of interest to our users and to job candidates. We may use the Active Information or Passive Information the subscribers and candidates provide to us to contact you about changes to our Site and Service, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you might find valuable, as well as to provide or enhance features of our Site and Service. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information from us, please  **[contact us](http://contact-us/)**.

We also use Passive Information to gather information about our users and customers candidates to enhance and design our Site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use. Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit our Site, when they visit and how they use our service. We do not connect any of this information to your or candidates personal information or email address.

**Sharing Information with Others**  
In addition to as described above, we may share Subscriber Information with others in the following situations without additional notice to or consent by you.

**Business Transactions**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might become involved in financing transactions or business transactions involving the sale or license of our assets or business units. In either case, Subscriber Information often is disclosed on a confidential basis or is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the Subscriber consents otherwise). Also, in the event the Company is merged with another company or acquired, or substantially all of its assets are acquired, Subscriber Information will be one of the transferred assets.

Protection of HRBoss and Others: We release Subscriber or Candidates Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or legitimate requests of law enforcement officials; enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our users, job candidates or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. This does not, however, include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from Subscribers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.  
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may disclose anonymous Passive Information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns, based on aggregate user statistics to advertisers on our Site or others.

**Security of Subscriber Information**  
We secure your Subscriber and Candidates Information by using commercially reasonable, industry-standard measures to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss, disclosure or destruction thereof. However, even very good security measures may fail to prevent computer hacking or other breaches of security, and we can provide no guarantees that the same will not occur. Additionally, our postings on this Site and other communications you may have with us via email or regular mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through those means.

**Other Websites**  
You and Candidates may be able to access other websites through our Site and/or Service. When you or candidates do so you are thereby subject to those other sites policies regarding privacy and data collection and you should read those sites’ privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. When you choose to visit such sites, you should read their privacy policies and terms of service to make sure you agree with them.

**Opting Out/Correcting or Deleting Personal Information**  
If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you or if you or any of your candidates wish to delete or correct your information, please  **[contact us](http://contact-us/)**.

**Enforcement**  
We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
Our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service may change from time to time. HRBoss reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify this Privacy Policy at any time and you will be responsible for reviewing and becoming familiar with any such modifications. Your use of the Site and/or the Service following such modification constitutes Subscriber's acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Agreement as modified. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you candidates and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of Subscriber and candidate information collected in the past without the consent of affected Subscribers and candidates.
